<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SPOON Documentation on SPOON Site Documentation</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SPOON Documentation on SPOON Site Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 18:36:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulk Upload Process</title>
      <link>/user/bulk-upload-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/user/bulk-upload-process/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can bulk upload any kind of file to SPOON inside of a zipped folder.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Guide</title>
      <link>/dev/developersguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/developersguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide goes over various issues developers would be concerned with, such as how to setup their IDE, what libraries are used, etc.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are instructions on how to get an instance of the site to run on your personal machine.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Guide</title>
      <link>/user/userguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/user/userguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The user guide is in the application help system.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>/dev/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/architecture/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide describes the high-level design of the server and client architecture.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Submission Forms</title>
      <link>/applicationadmin/customsubmissionforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/applicationadmin/customsubmissionforms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Custom Submission Forms are used when you want to present a custom look and feel to the user when they submit an entry.  You can add a form with many required or optional fields depending on the Entry Type of the submission.  This form is then shown to the user when they are presented with the fields for a new entry of that type.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting a New Component</title>
      <link>/user/quick-overview-of-submitting-a-new-component/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/user/quick-overview-of-submitting-a-new-component/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article briefly explains how to submit an entry onto SPOON
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplans</title>
      <link>/applicationadmin/workplans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/applicationadmin/workplans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide reviews how to create and manage a workplan.
 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/docker/</guid>
      <description>The SPOON application contains a Dockerfile in order to build Docker images. There are two dockerfiles in the repo. One is for development which is used by Jenkins to deploy the application for testing of new features. The other dockerfile is for the release build. These can be found in the repo at https://github.com/spoonsite/spoon/tree/master/Docker.
SPOON also automatically builds release versions of the application for consumption by users. These builds are available on Docker Hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-end Code Standards</title>
      <link>/dev/front-end-code-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/front-end-code-standard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are the agreed-upon standards for this project.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit Legend</title>
      <link>/user/unitlegend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/user/unitlegend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the legend for commonly confused unit names and acronyms.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administrator Guide</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/administratorguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/administratorguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article gives further instructions on setting up and configuring the web application.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Migration Guide</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/datamigrationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/datamigrationguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide provide help for importing data from external sources as well as
moving data from one instance to another instance.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Interface Guide</title>
      <link>/dev/uiguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/uiguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are general guidelines on what the look of SPOON should be.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version Migration</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/versionmigrationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/versionmigrationguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide details changes and upgrades that have happened from version to version.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Code Standard</title>
      <link>/dev/server-code-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/server-code-standard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are special notes when making additions to the server-side code.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Roles</title>
      <link>/applicationadmin/securityroles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 11:30:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/applicationadmin/securityroles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Security Roles define what permissions users get in the application.  Several default roles are set up with default permissions and are listed below.  These can be reset to default or altered as needed.  New roles can also be added.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluators Guide</title>
      <link>/evaluations/evaluator/storefront-evaluators-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/evaluations/evaluator/storefront-evaluators-guide/</guid>
      <description>This is a complete overview of the user interface to make an Evaluation on SPOON. Note: 2.6 Introduced some UI changes however, processes and concepts are the same.
TL;DR  Administrators create and publish evaluations. Evaluators fill out evaluations. While editing an evaluation you will not see exactly what the user sees. The user sees things bundled under a Details tab and an Evaluation tab. In an evaluation everything under the Entry section applies to that Details tab while everything under the Sections and Checklist sections apply to that Evaluations tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/evaluations/evaluator/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/evaluations/evaluator/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions by/for Evaluators Question
Do sub-sections save independent of other sub-sections?
Answer
Section (Eg. Architecture) may be broken in multiple sub-section. Saving save all sub-sections. So if your are edit more than one on multiple browser tabs. Keep in mind you changes will override changes in another tab. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to only edit in one browser tab and one browser at a time. Use change history to find resolve previous issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an Evaluation</title>
      <link>/evaluations/librarian/createevaluationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/evaluations/librarian/createevaluationguide/</guid>
      <description>This guide goes over creating Section templates, Checklist questions and templates, and Evaluation templates. This guide assumes a librarian has a basic understanding of what an entry is and has an entry that needs to be evaluated. Once the librarian has created checklists and templates, an evaluation can be created.
Who is this for? This guide is for anyone with the role of librarian or administrator. If unsure of current role(s), contact an administrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish an Evaluation</title>
      <link>/evaluations/librarian/publishinganevaluationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/evaluations/librarian/publishinganevaluationguide/</guid>
      <description>This guide goes over the different types of publishing and the various scenarios a librarian may run into when publishing an entry/evaluation. Different types of publishing:
 Entry publishing - publishes the entry summary only Partial publishing - publishes all default public fields except for those that have been marked as private. Full publishing - publishes all default public fields.  Reminder: an entry is a single entity that can have one to many evaluations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPOON</title>
      <link>/_header/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 18:36:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/_header/</guid>
      <description>SPOON Documentation </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>