<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>System Admin on Open Storefront Documentation</title>
    <link>/systemadmin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in System Admin on Open Storefront Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/systemadmin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/setup/</guid>
      <description>1. Installation 1.1 High level instructions for a fresh install Prior to the install, setup an Elasticsearch OR Solr instance and make sure it&#39;s running. Then, perform the following steps:
 Setup VM
 Install Java JDK 1.8
 Install Tomcat 7
 Integrate OpenAM Agent
 Deploy Application
 Configure Application
 Restart Tomcat (To pick up configuration changes)
 Import data
  1.2 Suggested VM Configuration The following is the recommended VM configuration:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/docker/</guid>
      <description>The SPOON application contains a Dockerfile in order to build Docker images. There are two dockerfiles in the repo. One is for development which is used by Jenkins to deploy the application for testing of new features. The other dockerfile is for the release build. These can be found in the repo at https://github.com/spoonsite/spoon/tree/master/Docker.
SPOON also automatically builds release versions of the application for consumption by users. These builds are available on Docker Hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administrator Guide</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/administratorguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/administratorguide/</guid>
      <description>1. Other Guides This guide has been organized into separate documents to make it easier to navigate. The focus of this document is for configuration. See other guides for other topics.
Architecture
Setup
Developer Guide
2. Configuration 2.1 Security 2.1.1 Supported Realms Configure in /var/openstorefront/config/shiro.ini
 INI (Properties File; Default)
Users are specified in the users section.
 LDAP (Example)
  [main] ldapRealm = org.apache.shiro.realm.ldap.JndiLdapRealm ldapRealm.userDnTemplate = uid={0},ou=users,dc=mycompany,dc=com ldapRealm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Migration Guide</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/datamigrationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/datamigrationguide/</guid>
      <description>This guide provide help for importing data from external sources as well as moving data from one instance to another instance.
1. Importing/Export (Third parties) The application provides set of standard format that it accepts to import Attributes/Categories as well as Entries. It also provides a set of custom formats that can have mappings applied. These custom formats allow taking a variety of data with so simple handling.
See Admin Tools -&amp;gt; Data Management -&amp;gt; Imports</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version Migration</title>
      <link>/systemadmin/versionmigrationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systemadmin/versionmigrationguide/</guid>
      <description>In general, you should always upgrade one version at a time in order. (IE. going from 2.2 to 2.4 then 2.2 to 2.3 then to 2.4) That way data migrations will occur in the proper order. If you start from the lastest version and have no data then migration is not needed.
Note: 2.6.3 For existing applications:
(Update var/openstorefront/config/shiro.ini)
Add:
/login/** = anon  /mobile/** = authc  /api/v1/resource/branding/current = anon  /api/v1/resource/securitypolicy = anon  /api/v1/resource/faq/* = anon  /api/v1/resource/faq = anon  /api/v1/resource/feedbacktickets = anon  Note: 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>